

## **CONTACT ME AT**

- Belarus, Minsk (Ready for remote or relocation
- klygun90@gmail.com
- (in) @hedonismv
- @hedonismv
- github.com/Hedonismv
- https://vitalyhomepage.vercel.app/

## **SKILLS SUMMARY**

JavaScript

React.is

Redux/ Mobx

Angularis + Rx.IS (entry level)

TypeScript

Next.is

CSS, Styled-Components, Chakra-ui, SASS LESS, Tailwind css

JWT. 02Auth

JSON, REST API, GraphQL

Node.js, Express

Firebase, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, MySQI

Webpack, CI/CD, JEST (unit test)

## **SOFTWARE SKILLS**

Figma, Photoshop, Illustrator. Blender 3D WebStorm, PyCharm, VSCODE, Sublime Trello, M. Teams, Slack, Notion Linux (Ubuntu), Windows, MacOS (prefer

## **LANGUAGES**

English **B1**Belarussian (Native)
Russian (Native)

# VITALI KLYHUN

## FRONTEND DEVELOPER

#### PERSONAL INFROMATION

I develop applications in different areas, for me the most important thing is new experience and knowledge. That's why I'm always practicing and learning new information not only in development, but also in economics, advertising and startups.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Frontend Developer**

Sheri & Freelance | March 2021 - present

- Developed frontend with React.js, Next.js + Redux, Redux-thunk
- Developed backend with Node.js + express, MongoDB
- Made mobile-first adaptive and responsive web-apps.
- Made SEO promotion for websites.
- Designed in Figma some elements of the website.

#### Co-founder of web studio

Taswiq Studio | August 2019 - November 2020

- Developed marketing plans and digital marketing
- Controlled the price policy
- Created new products and services
- Signed contracts and created commercial proposals
- Developed frontend with JavaScript and PHP

#### **EDUCATIONAL HISTORY**

#### **Belarussian State Economic University**

Marketing - economics specialist | 2019 - 2023 (Distance learning)

## **Branch of the Belarusian University of Trade and Economics of Consumer Cooperation**

Marketing - economics specialist | 2017 - 2019

#### **COURSES**

#### **GraphQL/Apollo school**

GraphQL | 2022

#### **MBA Marketing**

Digital Marketing | 2022

#### **Udemy**

React.js, Next.js, JavaScript, Node.js, Docker, Redux | 2021-2022

#### **Teach Me Skills**

Python3 / Django | 2020